电影里 德古拉身着斗篷...
In the movies, Dracula wears a cape...
...某个英国佬靠十字架和圣水打发一天的时间...
...and some old English guy always manages to save the day...
...总是在紧要关头化险为夷
...at the last minute with crosses and holy water.
大家都知道那种电影是鬼扯淡
But everybody knows the movies are full of shit.
事实上他的死对头是刀锋战士
The truth is it started with Blade, and it ended with him.
我们其他人只是凑热闹而已
The rest of us were just along for the ride.
(叙利亚 沙漠)
这是什么鬼玩意
What's this chicken scratch?
是楔形文
It's cuneiform.
有四千年的历史
It's about 4000 years old.
- 我们为什么来这里?  - 因为这里是文明的摇篮
- So why here?  - Because this is the cradle of civilization.
他应该会喜欢这里
He would have been comfortable here.
我不知道 丹 看起来又是个死胡同
I don't know, Dan. This seems like another dead end.
- 我们下面有东西  - 找到手表了吗?
- There's something beneath us.  - You find a watch?
那是尸体吗?
Is it a body?
各位?
Guys?
行动
Go.
该死 我的天啊
What the fuck? Motherfucker!
今晚 艾嘉·文斯 法庭心理医生...
Tonight, Dr. Edgar Vance, forensic psychiatrist...
...纽约时报畅销书作者:
...and author of the New York Times bestseller:
主题是人类健康之整体突破
The Whole Being Breakthrough.
同时请到警察局长马丁·维里德
Also with us, Martin Vreede, chief of police.
下个小时将接受观众热线...
They'll be here for the next hour, and they'll be taking your calls...
...请观赏班特利现场开讲节目
...next on Bentley Tittle Live.
好的 文斯医生 你是心理医生和生化科学家...
Okay, Dr. Vance, you are a psychiatrist and a biochemist...
...是吗?
...isn't that true?
是的 班特利 我两者皆是
Yes, uh, Bentley, I am both.
只在一个理由之下我坚信 真正的健康的身体...
And it's for a reason. I have always believed that true health can only be achieved...
...只有在身体跟心理的充分调和之下
...if we reconcile the body and the mind.
而且 为了做到这点 我们还必须排除一些不好的情绪
And, of course, in order to do that, we have to get rid of a lot of old notions.
好的 怎么分辨吸血鬼?
Okay, and how does that fit in with vampires?
嗯 有关于这个吸血鬼的传说 我们正在研究的...
Uh, in the case of vampires, we're dealing with creatures that are the repositories...
...对于宗教团体而言他是一种禁忌
...of some of our most taboo thoughts.
- 好的  - 是一种残暴凶狠的性格
- Okay.  - Predatory rage.
- 是的  - 性虐待狂
- Yeah.  - Sexual sadism.
- 性冲动?  - 性虐待狂
- Sexual?  - Sexual sadism.
这些都潜藏于人的内心深处
These are very scary subjects for people to own up to, and they're right inside.
所以 一般人都把这种事 当作借口来推卸责任
So, what you're saying is we pass the buck onto someone else.
- 你说的一点都没错  - 那吸血鬼呢?
- You bet we do.  - And vampires?
好的 比如 有一种嗜血的血液疾病
Well, for instance, there's a hereditary blood disease.
在我的书里 我称之为嗜血狂
I talk about it in my book, it's called porphyria.
和疾病的状况很相似 有典型的吸血鬼特征
And the symptoms of this disease are remarkably similar to classic vampire traits.
一般贫血的人最容易得病
The people who suffer from this disease are anemic.
他们只在夜间活动 他们不能忍受阳光 无法承受大蒜的气味
They become intolerant to sunlight. They can't handle garlic.
大蒜? 维里德局长 好吧 您对所有的传闻...
Garlic? Chief Vreede, okay, what's your take on all these rumors...
...近来的吸血鬼传闻你怎么评论? 吸血鬼 吸血鬼到底是什么?
...we've been hearing about vampires? Vampires. Vampires! What?
唯一让我担心的吸血鬼 就是身体检查要抽血 哈哈哈
The only vampires I'm worried about are the ones passing the bar exam. Ha-ha-ha.
咳咳
Ahem.
认真说来 如果真有吸血鬼 也还没有发现过他们的踪迹
Seriously though, if vampires existed, don't you think we would've found them by now?
严格来说街上也不是那么平静
The truth is, our streets have never been safer.
诸如自杀案 凶杀案 各式各样的罪犯充斥于各个角落
Homicides, assaults, violent crime is down across the board.
民众应该关心的是...
People wanna be concerned...
...那个叫刀锋战士的罪犯
...they should focus in on characters like this Blade criminal.
这就是我想了解的
That's the guy I wanna hear about.
我想了解刀锋 他是个什么样的人?
I wanna hear about this character Blade. What about him?
他是个精神异常的罪犯
He's a sociopath that we've been pursuing.
刀锋他是个麻烦人物
Blade is a troubled individual.
我知道他心里认为...
I understand that he is under the impression...
...世界饱受吸血鬼的威胁
...that there is a vast conspiracy of vampires.
嘿 嘿 是啊
Heh, heh. Yeah.
你必须相信 吸血鬼是活在我们身边
You've got to look at the psychiatric underpinnings of a belief like that.
同时他认为 他自己是个魔鬼的克星
Odds are, he believes that he is out there slaying monsters.
- 很好  - 至于他的做法呢...
- Mm-hm.  - But what he's really doing...
...其实他是想消除他自己内心的魔障
...is trying to kill aspects of himself.
《刀锋战士3：三位一体》
我在石脊天桥上
I'm on the Stonebridge overpass.
收到 我往西走 在你下面
Got it. Heading westbound. I'm just beneath you.
跳下来
Go.
(紫外线)
快点!
Come on!
松开了 拉!
I got him. Pull!
可以了吗?
You all right, man?
他有枪!
He's got a gun!
- 哦 天哪!  - 啊!
- Oh, my God!  - Aah!
你被银剑刺中了
Staked you with silver.
怎么不会化成灰烬?
Why aren't you ash?
你怎么还是一样笨?
Why aren't you smarter?
我不是吸血鬼 笨蛋!
Not a vampire, dumb shit!
你被骗了
Set your sorry ass up.
嗯
Hm.
该死
Damn.
噢 刀锋战士
Oh, Blade.
今晚到底是怎么回事?
What the fuck happened tonight?
我怎么知道?
How should I know?
他是人类
He was human.
太粗心了 刀锋 杀吸血鬼不留痕迹
You're getting reckless, Blade. Killing vampires is clean.
灰烬不能当证据
They ash, don't leave any evidence behind.
杀人可麻烦了
Killing humans is messy.
最好没目击者
You better hope nobody ID'd you.
这东西很好用
This worked really good.
- 这是什么东西?  - 你的新型免疫血清
- What's this?  - A new delivery system for your serum.
气泡式吸入剂
It's an effervescent inhaler.
只要咬住罐口
Just bite down on the mouth guard.
它会自动送药
Delivery's automatic.
我的朋友设计的
Some friends of mine made it.
嗯 朋友?
Hm. Friends?
是的 你应该记得?
Yeah. You remember those?
枪战激烈 汽车撞毁...
It was horrible. The one car crashed...
...穿长袍的猛开枪
...then the guy in the coat shot the other guy.
- 看上去血流成河  - 谢谢
- It looked like there was a lot of blood.  - Thank you.
这只是今晚枪战的一小部分...
That was just a taste of the mayhem that occurred...
...枪战 造成至少四人死亡
...during tonight's brazen shootout that left at least four people dead.
现在 一位市民拍下整个过程
Now, apparently, an anonymous citizen captured the whole event on video.
嘿 雷 听说有线索了
Hey, Ray. Hey, we got a lead.
赶飞机去
Let's catch a plane, Wilson.
我们去逮他们
Time to take these cowboys down.
我就是这个意思
That's what I'm talking about.
他在做什么?
What's he been doing?
猛吃
Fuck-all. Just feeding.
已经吸干五个人了
Been through five of them so far.
警卫人手够吗
You think we have enough security?
他不是被我们抓来的 他自己送上门来的
We didn't capture him, he allowed us to take him in.
知道吗? 我要进去
You understand? I'm gonna go in.
你不该把我唤醒的
You shouldn't have woken me.
情非得已
We had to.
你的血 圣餐能解救我们
Your blood, your sacrament, can set us free now.
你认为我在乎你们吗?
What makes you think I care?
你的族人需要你
Your people need you.
族人?
My people?
你们只是先祖的行尸走肉
You're nothing but shadows of your former selves.
堕落到如此不堪的地步
Look how far you have fallen.
世界改变了
The world's changed since your time.
人类有了新猎人
The humans have a new hunter.
刀锋战士
Blade.
你要我去杀他 是吗?
And you'd like me to kill him, wouldn't you?
对
Yes.
你不能抗拒的诅咒
You can't fight the curse
你不能联系医生
You can't call the doctor
就那张吗?
这个我也要.
这家伙该培养点别的兴趣.
最好不要.
与渴爱狂
With the thirsty love guzzler
在黑暗的一面 不要害怕宝贝
From the dark side, baby Don't be afraid
你不能抗拒的渴望
You can't fight the thirst
目标往西移动
Subject is heading west.
看到他了
Got him.
恭喜 你出名了
Congratulations. You're famous.
我们被拍个正着
Somebody nailed us.
报纸电视到处都是你的面孔
Your face is all over the papers and television.
媒体吃尽
Media's eating it up.
- 谁在乎  - 你应该在乎
- Like I care.  - Well, you should.
杀人事件...
Something like this, taking out a human...
...全世界都在乎...
...as far as the rest of the world is concerned...
...你已经成了头号公敌
...you're public enemy number one.
我不知道有这种人气排行榜
Didn't know this was a popularity contest.
该死 刀锋 你还不知道他们的诡计吗?
Damn it, Blade, don't you see what they're doing?
他们想引起群众对你的公愤
They're waging a goddamn P.R. campaign.
现在我们不只要担心吸血鬼...
Now it's not just vampires we gotta worry about...
...我们还必须跟全世界对抗
...we're gonna have to take on the rest of the world too.
你担心太多了 老头
You worry too much, old man.
"担心" 我们才能活到今天
It's why we're still alive, goddamn it.
你出生前我已经在杀吸血鬼 刀锋
I've been doing this since before you were born, Blade.
我把你当儿子
You're like a son to me.
抱歉 我已经老了
I'm sorry I got old on you.
看你孤单一个人被敌人包围
I see you alone, surrounded by enemies.
我心里很难过
And it breaks my heart.
我们无法单独打赢这场战争的
We can't win this war alone.
看看这些人 他只给了我一双邪恶眼睛 来吧 这个人怎么样?
Look at it. He just gave me the evil eye. Come on, man. What about that guy?
- 宝贝 你好!  - 快点 别胡闹!
- Prostitute, baby. Whoo-hoo!  - Come on! Quit fucking around!
肚子饿到想吃人
I'm hungry and I want to eat somebody.
- 这个怎么样?  - 这个人尝起来一定很像芝多司
- What about him?  - No fatties. They taste like Cheetos.
我不知道 我喜欢他
I don't know. I like him.
等等 那是什么? 这个看起来像皱巴巴的苹果
Wait. What about that? Shrunken apple-headed bitch.
无聊 太无聊了
That fucking sorry ass over there.
他妈的给我 男人! 快点选一个吧 上帝!
Fucking blow me, man! Just pick one already. Jesus Christ!
哦 得了吧! 得了吧!
Oh, got it! Got it!
宝贝餐
Baby on board.
哦 你们看看那里的美食
Oh, looks like we got ourselves a combo meal!
小妞 小妞 小妞
Chickie, chickie, chickie.
哦 宝贝!
Oh, yeah, baby!
晚餐吃什么?
What's for dinner?
嘿 嘿 嘿 漂亮的女士
Heh, heh. Hey, pretty lady.
不! 不!
No! No!
不!
No!
会痛要叫啊 辣妹
Scream if this hurts, chica.
- 哈哈哈!  - 啊!
- Ha, ha, ha!  - Aah!
"去死"?
"Fuck you"?
大蒜!
Garlic!
来啊!
Come on!
会痛要叫啊 帅哥
Scream if this hurts, chica.
怎么回事?
What is it?
你担心的事发生了
What you were worried about.
动作快 动作快!
Let's go, let's go!
开火!
Shoot to kill!
(数据保护程序启动  1号工作站保护启动)
动根手指头你就死定了
Move a finger, and you're dead.
动这根可以吗?
How's about this one?
他启动爆炸装置了!
He's got something in his hand!
大家快离开 刀锋
Get out, Blade!
该死!
Shit!
里面发生什么事情了?
What's going on in there?
谁可以告诉我!
Somebody talk to me!
站着别动!
Hold it right there!
别开枪 别开枪
Don't shoot, don't shoot.
(警察局)
起床 懒猪
Rise and shine, sleepyhead.
FBI探员康柏蓝和哈尔
Special agents Ray Cumberland, Wilson Hale. FBI.
我们盯你很久了
We've been tracking you a long time.
惠斯勒呢
Whistler.
死了
Dead.
跟你其他受害人一样
Just like all your victims.
你杀了多少人 刀锋?
How many people have you killed, Blade?
30? 40? 50人?
Thirty? Forty? Fifty?
1182人
1182.
但都是他们的爪牙
But they were all familiars.
或同伙
People who work with them.
"他们" 指的是吸血鬼吗?
Oh. And by "them," you mean vampires, right?
你怎么杀死他们的 铁汉?
So how do you kill these bloodsuckers, tough guy?
可不可以告诉我们
Maybe you can give us some pointers.
- 用太阳光吗?  - 是不是用太阳光?
- You can stake them, right?  - What about sunlight?
- 他们不是不能感受阳光吗?  - 怎么办? 他们还工作吗?
- They ain't feeling sunlight right?  - What about crosses? Do they still work?
- 在这个时代?  - 我不知道 雷
- In this day and age?  - I don't know, Ray.
这些吸血鬼是不是都是犹太人?
What if Mr. Homey Vampire's like Jewish?
- 哈哈 这才是重点  - 嘿 嘿
- Ha, ha. That's a good point.  - Heh, heh.
大蒜怎么样? 这个好像对吸血鬼才有效?
And what about garlic? Does that work on Hindu vampires?
你的意思是说用大便治病?
Or do you need like saffron or some shit?
- 说得好  - 谢谢
- That was quick.  - Thank you.
你继续自欺欺人吧 刀锋
You can keep doing your song and dance as long as you want, Blade.
我们是不会相信的
It's not gonna play.
我们知道你是什么
We know what you are.
你是个冷血杀手
You're a stone-cold killer.
而且变态
And you're sick as fuck.
把他交给专家诊断
Let's leave the diagnosis to the professionals.
你好 刀锋
Hello, Blade.
我是文斯医生
My name is Dr. Vance.
我负责对你做心理评估
I've been charged with giving you a psychiatric evaluation.
两位 可以回避一下吗?
Gentlemen, would you mind giving us just a couple of minutes alone?
交给你了
He's all yours.
我知道你心里很害怕...
I know you must find this very frightening...
...但请相信我是来帮助你的
...but I want you to know that I'm here to help.
为了让我能够帮助你...
And in order for me to do that...
...我得先问你几个问题
...I'm gonna have to ask you a couple of questions.
可以吗?
Okay?
你知道吗 刀锋 你在里面被关了几天...
Heh. You know, Blade, the darnedest thing. I was signing in at Security...
...你可能不知道今天是几号了
...and couldn't remember the date.
请问今天是几号?
Do you know what day it is?
总统是谁?
How about the president?
你知道他在哪里吗?
You know who that is?
谁是白宫主人?
Who's in the White House right now?
一个痞子
An asshole.
可以跟我谈谈吸血鬼吗
I think somebody here wants to talk about vampires.
吸血鬼
Vampires.
这个问题有点笨
For everyone else, it's kind of silly.
我有一个蜡像做的吸血鬼已经七年了
I had a set of wax teeth when I was 7 years old.
很好玩
It was fun.
我做个旁观者
I could be somebody else.
倒是想听听你说吸血鬼的事
But I wanna hear you talk about vampires.
你可以对我说吗
What can you tell me about them?
他们存在
They exist.
你也是其中之一吗?
Are you one of them?
有时候他们只是吓到而已...
Sometimes the scariest monster of all...
...被一面镜子
...is the one in the mirror.
告诉我关于嗜血的事
Tell me about blood.
血的滋味怎么样...
When you drink blood...
...吸血时你会性亢奋吗?
...do you ever feel sexually aroused?
我觉得吸血行为...
It just strikes me that this business of vampirism...
...跟性错乱有强烈关连
...has a very strong element of sexual confusion.
算是一种交换体液行为
Nuzzling into someone's neck.
夜间到访...
A nocturnal visit...
...是一种肉体上甜美的幻想症
...with promises of delicious physical intimacy.\
非常甜美的口水...
The very sweet taste of saliva...
...和皮肤融合
...mixed with skin.
对我来说很棒
Oh. Sounds good to me.
他是从哪里来的?
But where's it come from?
我很想知道
That's what I wanna know.
我很好奇 你跟你母亲的关系怎么样
And I'm starting to wonder what your relationship with your mother was like.
你们很亲密吗?
Were the two of you very close?
他是神经病
He's psychotic.
- 错不了  - 为大家好...
- No shit.  - For his safety and for the public's...
...他应该送神经病院…
...l'm recommending he be transferred to County Psychiatric...
他妈的! 他是我的犯人
Fuck that! That man is my prisoner.
他是与很多罪案有关的罪犯
He's wanted in connection with a laundry list of crimes.
等一等 先生们 他现在在我的辖区
Hold on, gentlemen. We're in my jurisdiction now.
有意见请跟地方法官申诉
Got a problem with that, you talk to the local magistrate.
那个人是我的犯人! 别他妈的干涉我的事!
That man is my prisoner! Don't fuck with my thing!
院方会派一组人来接他
There's a team from the hospital effecting the transfer immediately.
你应该跟我们合作才对 长官
You're supposed to be working with us, chief.
这次不一样
Not this time.
这东西会让你乖乖合作
This is just a little something to keep you compliant.
一般人只要200到300毫克...
The usual dose for this sort of thing is 200, 300 milligrams...
...但像你这种人高马大的杂种...
...but I think with a big, strapping hybrid like yourself...
...剂量应该提高到2000毫克
...l'll kick it up to a couple thousand.
你不怕打针吧?
You don't have a problem with needles, do you?
那里
There.
不怎么痛 不是吗?
That wasn't so bad, was it?
噢 你好虚弱
Ooh. You're weak.
需要血清是吧
In need of your serum.
这种感觉一定很不好
That must be a bad feeling.
我的意思是 很难想像...
I mean, who would've imagined...
...我这种凡夫俗子竟比你强
...that a mere human like me could have overpowered you.
你跟他们是一伙的
You're one of them.
吸血帮
A familiar.
加入已经五年了
Going on five years now.
时机快成熟了 刀锋
It's the endgame, Blade.
他们的计划到了成熟阶段
All their plans are coming to fruition.
你不妨放轻松 看好戏上场?
Why don't you just sit back and enjoy the show?
我恨吸血帮
I hate familiars.
所以我们还活着 妈的
It's why we're still alive, goddamn it.
我把你当自己的儿子
You're like a son to me.
抱歉 我老了
I'm sorry I got old on you.
看到你孤单一人被敌人包围
I see you alone, surrounded by enemies.
我心里很难过
It breaks my heart.
嗨 刀锋
Hi, Blade.
很高兴又见面了
So glad to finally meet you.
我很崇拜你
I am such a fan.
我喜欢你的刺青
I like your tattoos.
它们有特殊意义吗
Do they mean anything
猪头
Stupid.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
累吗?
Are you tired?
虚弱吗
You're weak.
人类被我们骗得团团转
We moved the humans around.
像棋盘上的卒子
Like pawns.
我们利用他们...
We used them...
...将你变成过街老鼠
...to flush you out.
你并不高大嘛
You're not so big.
孤苦无依啊 刀锋
You're all alone, Blade.
现在没有人会来救你
No one's gonna help you now.
(操 你)
- 晚安 小姐们  - 汉尼拔·金恩!
- Evening, ladies.  - Hannibal King!
起来 我们救你
Wake up. This is your rescue.
快走
Go!
站住
Freeze!
惠斯勒
Whistler!
往这边
This way!
刀锋 你死定了
Blade! You're dead!
趴下
Get down!
刀锋
Blade.
嘿 嘿 哇 哇 哇
Hey, hey. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
你要去哪里? 他要去哪里?
Where are you going? Where the fuck is he going?
我们是来救他的!
This is supposed to be a rescue!
回来 回来
Get back, get back!
- 我们被困住了  - 在角落没办法开枪
- We're pinned down.  - I can't shoot around corners.
我可以
I can.
好了 这下完蛋了
Okay. We're fucked.
没事的
We're fine.
我忘了我的剑
Forgot my sword.
毕竟我们是士兵
We are soldiers, after all
毕竟我们不会丢掉荣誉
Down by honor we won't fall. After all
喔!
Whoo!
快上车
Come on!
最后进来
Comin'out the back end
在你死之前 他引导你
Dead at you. He throwin'that hot lead at you
鼓动下属 喝XO 金属吸气剂
Swang affiliate, XO sip, a gold getter
其他人在一起 我是一个冷酷杀手
With the rest together. I'm a cold killer
这是"我反对的世界"
It's "Me Against the World" like 2Pac
像你听到的:"我准备好去死"
And like Biggie. I'm "Ready to Die" for what you got
爱碧
Abby.
盯上他了
We got him.
我们马上到达
We'll be there soon.
你们是什么人?
Who the hell are you people?
我叫汉尼拔·金恩
Well, my name is Hannibal King.
这个女豪杰叫爱碧嘉
And this little hellion right here is Abigail.
惠斯勒的女儿
Whistler's daughter.
我以为惠斯勒家被满门抄斩了
I thought the vampires killed Whistler's family.
没错 但我是非婚生子女
They did. I was born later out of wedlock.
成年后 才找到老爸认祖归宗的
When I came of age, I tracked my dad down, and I told him I wanted in.
从此与吸血鬼誓不两立
Been doing it ever since.
欢迎光临蜂巢之家
Welcome to the honeycomb hideout.
你哪来的经费?
How do you bankroll this operation?
陪有钱老头睡觉啊
I date a lot of older men.
来吧 我是开玩笑的
Come on, man, I'm joking.
这位是德克斯
You met Dex.
他是海吉斯
This is Hedges.
桑莫菲 新吸入式血清发明人
Sommerfield. She's the one who built that new serum inhaler of yours.
刚刚那位女孩是她女儿柔伊
That runt you saw earlier, that was Sommerfield's daughter. Zoe.
我们自称夜行者
We call ourselves the Nightstalkers.
听起来像过气的卡通人物
Hm. Sounds like rejects from a Saturday morning cartoon.
本想叫夜魔侠 但有人先用了
We were gonna go with the Care Bears, but that was taken.
- 这里总共有多少人?  - 够多了
- How many of you are there?  - There's enough.
我们采用暗桩作业
We operate in sleeper cells.
一个倒下 马上有人递补
When one goes down, another cell activates to pick up the slack.
我们是你的生力军
Consider us your reinforcements.
什么 你们这些业余的能帮助我吗?
What, you amateurs are supposed to be helping me?
你们?
Heh. You?
看看你们的样子
Look at you.
你们太嫩了
You're kids.
怎么上大场面
You're not ready to roll with this.
看你们的打扮
I mean, look at the way you're dressed.
这也算一种战术吗?
What, that's supposed to be tactical?
这是什么? 干死你! 想笑死人吗?
What is this? What is that? Fuck you! It's a joke, huh?
搞什么鬼? 你们以为好玩吗?
What the fuck is wrong with y'all? Y'all think this is a joke?
- 你们以为是搞笑剧吗?  - 好的 第一 你这态度很失礼
- You think this is a fucking sitcom?  - Okay, first off, that's just rude.
第二 我们刚刚救了你一命
Second, I'm pretty sure we saved your ass back there.
我很感动
Mm. I'm impressed.
刀锋 我父亲交代要我们帮你
Look, Blade, my father meant for us to help you.
不满意也只好接受
Like it or not, we are all you got.
你们怎么知道如何猎杀吸血鬼?
What the hell makes you think you know about hunting vampires?
一个最简单的道理
Well, here's for starters.
我以前是吸血鬼
I used to be one.
面试可以通过了吗?
Do I pass the audition?
菜鸟
Rookies.
该死的汉尼拔
Fucking Hannibal King!
当初我应该把他撕成碎片
I should've ripped his bleeding heart out when I had the chance!
我们有刀锋
We had Blade.
我们抓到他
We had him!
不要幸灾乐祸的样子 艾许
And don't tell me "I told you so," Asher.
什么是错? 你该休息了?
What's wrong, half-pint? You need a timeout?
你算老几
Blow me.
这次输得有够难看
We got caught with our pants down.
难看
Pants down?
简直是被强暴
They pretty much fucking ass-raped us.
你不是很喜欢吗
Oh, you loved it.
他知道了吗
Has he been told?
知道你们一败涂地?
About your failure?
当然知道
Yes.
看来我得亲自出马了
Maybe it's time I joined the game.
你知道哪种女人最危险?
You know the kind of woman that just screams trouble?
你一看就知道她招惹不得...
You see her, and every warning bell in your brain starts going off...
...但你忍不住还是跟她要电话
...but you still manage to ask for her number.
碰到这种女人我就缴械了
Well, that's all I ever hook up with.
但这女人...
But this betty...
...天下没一个女人是她的对手
...whoa, she blew them all away in the shitstorm sweepstakes.
她叫丹妮卡·泰勒斯
Her name is Danica Talos.
你以前见过
You met her earlier.
她与众不同 撩牙长在阴道里
And unlike typical vampires, her fangs are located in her vagina.
继续看
Moving on.
她左边那个是她哥哥 艾许
The man on her left is her brother, Asher.
这个是加科·格日伍德
And this walking diaper stain is Jarko Grimwood.
我在酒吧钓上她...
I picked Danica up in a bar...
...在一起五年...
...and spent the next five years playing hide-and-go-suck...
...从头到尾当她的性奴隶
...as her little vampire cabana boy.
最后爱碧嘉找到了我
Eventually, Abigail found me.
病治好了我成了吸血鬼杀手
Sommerfield managed to treat me with a cure, and now I kill them.
我算是彻底脱胎换骨
And that's basically turning a frown upside down.
我们必须集合所有资源 刀锋
We need to pool our resources, Blade.
"我们"?
"We"?
是的 我们
Yeah, we.
他重现江湖了
He's come back.
你看看
Take a look at this.
漫画你也当真
You gotta be kidding me.
- 你们从哪里找到这些东西?  - 大部分是偷来的
- Where'd you guys get this stuff?  - I stole most of it.
这是从地下挖出来的一些珍藏 这是他的一件盔甲 石器...
Danica had a huge collection. He had stone work...
...铁器 艺术品
...iron work, weaponry, art.
有图像有雕刻通通都是
This stuff that shows up everywhere, this symbol, this glyph.
它的东西都在这 这些都是真的
It's on everything in here. He is real.
你挖掘的所有神话...
You dig beneath all the myths, all the layers of bullshit...
...五百年前谜样的文化遗物...
...that have cluttered our culture for the last 500 years...
...这些几乎都是真实的
...and eventually, you're gonna strike the truth.
所以电影是真的
So the movies are true.
不止是电影 漫画 童话故事都是真的
The movies are just a comforting fairytale compared to the real deal.
他写了一个好故事
Bram Stoker, he wrote a good yarn.
1897年我们才发现他 摩西那个时代
But the events he described back in 1897... God, that was just a tiny piece of the mosaic.
可是他应该存在于更早更早之前
The real Dracula, his origins, date back much, much earlier then that.
- 多早?  - 根据七百年前的遗迹
- How early?  - Try 6 or 7 thousand years.
这是他的盔甲
This is a piece of his armor.
有了它 我们根据它勾勒出他的样子
With it, we were able to extrapolate a basic idea of what this fucker looked like.
你再看看这个
Check this out.
德古拉只是他的化名之一
Dracula's only one of the names he's gone by.
巴比伦人把他当阎罗王 现在称他为德瑞克
The Babylonians worshipped him as Dagon, and now they call him Drake.
根据传说他生于古叙利亚
If you believe in the legends, he was born in ancient Sumeria.
没人知道他源自哪里
Nobody really knows the specifics of his origin, but we do know this:
只知道他是吸血鬼的始祖
He was the first of his kind.
夜行人种的大长老
The patriarch of Hominus nocturna.
天生完美无暇
He was born perfect.
跟大白鳖一样 完全不需要进化
And just like the great white shark, this guy has never had to evolve.
别被书或电影的
Forget the movies, forget the books.
快乐结局骗了
There's no happy ending with this guy.
直到今天他还在暗处活动...
He's been there, moving behind the scenes...
...从远古杀出一条血路活到今天...
...cutting a bloody fucking path through the ages, until suddenly...
...从未停歇...
...just like that...
...神出鬼没
...he up and disappeared.
我们听到一个谣言
And then we heard a rumor.
吸血鬼前段时间正找他
The vampires were searching for him.
有人说他已沉睡几百年...
Some say he'd been sleeping through the ages...
...退出了这个仇恨他的世界
...that he'd retreated from a world he'd become disgusted with.\
半年前他在伊拉克被找到了
And according to our information, they found him in 1raq about six months ago.
他非常生气
And he was pissed.
你的橱窗里...
In the window....
有卖吸血鬼商品?
You sell vampire merchandise?
是的 看看嘛
Uh, yeah. Look around.
我们东西不少
We might have a few things.
有德古拉便当盒
We've got Dracula lunchboxes.
看到了吗?
Did you see those?
大头娃娃 钥匙圈
There's bobbleheads, key chains.
这多有趣
This is funny
大蒜每次都提醒我
The garlic gets me every time.
应有尽有
We've got just about anything.
还有吸血鬼按摩棒
Even vampire vibrators.
看看这个
Here. check this out.
"德古拉伯爵" 让你想哭 不是吗?
"Dracola." Makes you wanna cry, doesn't it?
你在找什么东西吗?
Was there something special you needed?
嘿 伙计
Hey, guy.
她在跟你说话
She's talking to you.
怎么了?
What?
想吻我吗 帅哥?
You wanna kiss me, pretty boy?
不想!
No!
- 为什么吵醒德古拉?  - 我们正想搞懂这点
- Why wake up Drake now?  - That's what we've been trying to figure out.
我还是吸血鬼时...
When I was under the fang...
...听他们说要找什么终极方案
...there used to be talk about some kind of vampire final solution.
但没道理毁掉食物来源啊
Never figured out why they'd wanna destroy their food source.
这毫无意义 对不?
That makes no sense, right?
他们不断想办法对付人类
They've always had plans for the human race.
看来 不管他们在做...
It seems likely that whatever they're cooking up...
...德古拉复出也是其中之一 面对事实...
...Drake's return is part of it. Let's face it...
...这场战争胜算不大
...we are fighting a losing battle here.
一年了不起杀他们几百个
So we kill a few hundred of them a year. Big deal.
但他们数量高达数万人
There are thousands of them out there, maybe tens of thousands.
我们必须要有新战术
We need a new tactic.
比如说?
Like what?
生物武器
A biological weapon.
针对你们看得见的人...
For you sighted people...
...这里有一段说明
...here's a little show-and-tell.
我从事合成DNA...
For the last year, I've been working with synthesized DNA...
...多年来创造出一种人造吸血鬼病毒
...in order to create an artificial virus targeted specifically at vampires.
我们称之为"晨星"
We're calling it DayStar.
你想想看 刀锋
Think about it, Blade.
我们可以将他们一举歼灭
We could wipe them all out in one single move.
那为什么不采取行动?
So, what's been holding you back?
但致命率不能达到百分之百
The lethality in vampires is still spotty.
我们需要一股更强的DNA
The bottom line is, we need a better strand of DNA to work with.
我们要德古拉的血液
We need Dracula's blood.
因为德古拉具有吸血鬼的血源...
Because Dracula is the progenitor of the vampire race...
...他的DNA最纯
...his DNA is still pure.
未曾经过数百世代变种的稀释
It hasn't been diluted by a hundred generations of selective mutation.
有了他的血"晨星"的效力可以达到百分百
We get his blood, we can boost DayStar's viral efficacy to 100 percect.
吸血鬼将全部灭绝
All the vampires go bye-bye.
所以 你想不想成为...
So can we just go right ahead and sign you up...
...我们的夜行者的荣誉会员?
...for one of our secret Nightstalker decoder rings?
哦 嗯...
Oh. Uh....
见鬼了... 各位帅哥辣妹...
Holy shit. Urn.... Gentlemen and hottie...
...各种致命武器...
...we have a wide assortment of ass-kickery...
...今天为你们展示
...for your viewing pleasure today.
各种口径大小的电子枪
Electronic pistol. Comes in a variety of tasty calibers.
爆炸性子弹
Explosive rounds.
里面是填充的是高浓缩紫外线
Yeah, but with a concentrated burst of UV light...
...不是标准的点发式
...instead of your standard hollow points.
我称之为日之犬
I call them sundogs.
海吉斯 秀点特别的
Hedges. Super Size me, sweetheart.
这把小BB枪是...
This little peashooter, it's a modified version...
...陆军个人战斗发射器的进化版
...of the Army's Objective Individual Combat Weapon.
日之犬 镖...
Pick your poison: sundogs, stakes...
...追热火箭
...heat-seeking mini rockets.
任何炮弹他都负责 帮你射出去
Basically, whatever gets you hard, this puppy will pump them out.
当然 射程比不上你那把剑...
Course, it doesn't have the range of a sword, but....
噢 别这样 这个…
Oh, God. Over here, we...
我们称之为紫外线弧
We call this the UV Arc.
两点接有强力紫外线雷射…
Whoa. Sorry. The two points are connected by a powerful UV laser...
- 海吉斯 以下我来说明  - 好的
- Hedges, I'll take it from here.  - Yes.
它的威力大概等于半个太阳
This bad boy is half as hot as the sun.
杀吸血鬼像切奶油一样轻松
It can cut through vampires like a knife through butter.
但德古拉的本事得仔细评估
We're still trying to sort out fact from fiction when it comes to Dracula.
他真能化成一阵烟吗?
Turning into mist? Kind of doubt it.
一般变形可能没问题
General shape-shifting? Maybe.
当然不是变成蝙蝠或狼...
Not into a bat or a wolf or anything like that...
...而是变成另一个人
...but another human, with practice, could be possible.
因为他的骨架与众不同
Because he wouldn't have a traditional skeletal structure.
像蛇一样由小块骨头组成…
Something more like a snake's, with thousands of tiny bones...
这点我有问题 海吉斯
I have a... I have a question about that, Hedges.
你是处男吗?
Have you ever been laid?
我经验丰富
Many times.
跟女人吗
With ladies.
该给他们一点压力了
Time for a little refresher.
吸血鬼统御上最脆弱的一环...
Weakest link in the vampire chain of command...
...就是他们帮内的人类
...has always been their familiars.
因为吸血鬼白天不能出来...
Since the vampires can't go out in the daylight...
...非法勾当都委托人类去办
...they get the humans to do all their dirty work.
威胁一下这些冒牌货...
We bleed the wannabes...
...迟早可以找到本尊
...sooner or later, they'll take us right to the real.
你的新车
I got you some new wheels.
好好爱护
You take care of it, now.
她正在工作
She's making playlists.
她打猎时喜欢听MP3
She likes to listen to MP3s when she hunts.
当成她的个人配乐 你知道吗?
It's like her own internal soundtrack, you know?
全都是现在孩子们最爱听的
Dark-core, trip hop, whatever kids are listening to these days.
你知道吗 我是大卫·哈斯霍夫的影迷?
Me, I'm more of a David Hasselhoff fan, you know?
你的头迟早会被甩掉的
Eventually, you know, your head is gonna pop off.
该死 不 不 求求你们
Fuck! No, no! Please! Please!
你们老大是谁?
Who's your handler?
我不知道 我发誓 我发誓!
I don't know my fucking handler. I swear. I swear!
哦 该死 求求你们了
Oh, shit! Please! Please! Aah!
是你的
Oh, it's you.
我帮你接
I'll take that.
快点 给我 快点
Come on. Let's go. Come on.
(文斯医生 来电)
喂?
Hello?
你好 我是文斯医生 你找我
Hello, this is Dr. Vance. You paged me.
嘿
Heh.
找你的 接啊
It's for you. Yeah, go ahead.
那位?
Hello?
啊!
Aah!
你知道 人有时候…
You know, at some point, you, uh...
应该去看看心理医生
You might wanna consider sitting down with somebody.
你懂得 分享一下心里的秘密
You know? Have a little share time.
碰触一下内心那份纯真
Kick back. Get in touch with your inner child. That sort of thing.
建议你 偶尔要眨一下眼睛
Also, just a thought, but you might wanna consider blinking once in a while.
抱歉 我今天吃太多糖
I'm sorry, I uh... l ate a lot of sugar today.
嘿
Hey.
闲人不能进去
You just can't walk in here like that. Unh!
抱歉 先生
Excuse me, sir.
不要那么做
Don't do that.
- 文斯呢?  - 很抱歉 文斯医生现在没空
- Where's Vance?  - I'm sorry, you can't see Dr. Vance now.
坐下
Sit.
有事吗?
Can I, uh... Can I help you?
记得我吗? 该我报仇了
Remember me? Time for payback.
好的 文斯 你知道些什么？
All right, Vance, what the hell do you know?
天啊 是他
Oh, Jesus. It's him.
爱碧 他是德瑞克
Abby, it's Drake!
你就是他们害怕的猎人
So you're the hunter they all fear.
- 难怪我有感觉  - 尽管开枪
- I had a feeling about you.  - Just shoot him!
开啊 刀锋
Go ahead, Blade.
我看你有没有种
Show me what you're made of.
天啊
Oh, my God!
他抓走我的孩子
He got my baby! Aah!
不 我的宝贝
No! My baby!
小心 日行者
Ah. Careful, Daywalker.
我知道你有...
I've been told about you...
...同情人类的弱点
...your weakness for humans.
你为什么杀文斯?
Why'd you kill Vance?
他已经没利用价值了
He'd outlived his purpose.
他死得其所
He died a good death.
干净 快速
Quick, clean.
你懂什么
I wouldn't know anything about that.
你会懂的
You will.
你怎么受得了阳光?
How are you able to survive in sunlight?
你没看过史托克的小说吗?
Haven't you read Stoker's fable?
我是吸血鬼的始祖
I was the first of the vampires.
我是独一无二的
I am unique.
- 所以他们找你帮忙  - 当然
- So that's why they brought you back.  - Of course.
我的血可以让他们成为日行者
They believe through me they could become Daywalkers.
看那些忙碌的人
Look at them down there.
像小虫子一样
Scurrying around like insects.
他们不懂战士的荣誉...
They don't know anything about honor or living by the sword...
...不像你和我
...not like you and I do.
他们可能懂何谓不朽吗?
Do you think they could ever grasp what it means to be immortal?
你不是不朽的
You're not immortal.
几百个吸血鬼讲过相同的话
I must have heard hundreds of you rodents make the same claim.
但都尝到我剑的滋味
Each one of them have tasted the end of my sword.
或许我会是下一个...
Perhaps I will too, then...
...但相信下次我们见面...
...but I think it is more likely, the next time we meet...
...你会倒在我面前
...you fall before mine.
接住
Catch!
乖
Cootchie-coo.
你有看到他吗? 我们输定了…
Did you see that guy? We're gonna lose, man. We're gonna...
该死
Oh! God!
我们会死得很难看
We're gonna fucking lose!
- 好的  - 嗯
- Okay.  - Ugh.
你想做什么 你跟其他的吸血鬼一样?
What did the one lesbian vampire say to the other?
- 闭嘴 金恩  - 二十天一次 哈哈
- Shut up, King.  - See you in 28 days. Ha, ha!
哇 哇 哇 等等 那是什么? 你想干什么?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on. What... What is that? What are you doing?
弹性蛋白 帮你止血
It's an elastic protein, okay? It's gonna stop the hemorrhaging.
好的 会痛吗?
Okay. Is it gonna hurt?
一点点刺痛
Yeah, it's gonna sting a little.
真的吗?
Really? Unh.
他妈的
Fuck me! Ow!
有一家人
I had a family once.
夫妻俩 两个女儿
Wife, two daughters.
那一晚来了一个流浪汉
Then a drifter came calling one evening.
一个吸血鬼
A vampire.
他先戏弄他们
He toyed with them first.
要我决定谁先死
Tried to make me decide which order they'd die in.
我猎杀吸血鬼很久了
I've been doing this a long time.
从你出生前已经开始
Since before you were born.
我不要你过这种生活 爱碧
I don't want this life for you, Abby.
刀锋
Hey, Blade.
我有个问题想问你
I got a question for you.
杀光所有吸血鬼后你想干什么
Say we're successful. Say we wipe out all the vampires.
然后呢?
What then, huh?
你想过这问题吗?
You ever ask yourself that?
很难想像你在社区里教空手道
I mean, somehow, I don't picture you teaching karate at the local Y.
他讨厌我 对吗?
He hates me, doesn't he?
没错
Yeah.
你为什么带着那个东西?
Why do you wear that symbol?
老习惯了
Old habits.
我以前是天主教学校的女学生
I was a good Catholic school girl.
- 我曾经是  - 我那个时候在对抗他
- Once.  - l was there when they crucified him.
他因赎罪而死
He died for their sins.
不是我的罪恶
Not mine.
那你的罪恶呢?
And what are your sins?
你在乎吗?
Would you care to confess them?
脱掉
Take it off.
为什么?
Why?
我会让你舒服
I will make you a better one.
有个古老传说:
There's an old saying:
"杀死了国王 侮辱了他
"Kill one man, you're a murderer.
杀了很多
Kill a million, a king.
杀光他们...
Kill them all...
...上帝"
...a God."
你为什么要吸这个
Why do you do that?
因为我体内有个坏东西
Because there's something bad inside of me.
这可以防止它跑出来
This keeps it from getting out.
你为什么不能当好人?
Why can't you just be nice?
因为世界对我不友善
Because the world isn't nice.
我知道吸血鬼躲在哪里
I found where the vampires are working.
生化医药企业
Biomedica Enterprises.
他们在大肆采购补给品
They've been buying up all sorts of supplies.
查查看
Check it out.
DNA聚合酵素
Taq polymerase.
骨髓成长素
Bone-marrow growth supplement.
基因排序酵素
Genetic-sequencing enzymes.
- 嗯  - 要派对纪念品吗?
- Hm.  - You want a party favor?
幸运7号 银子弹
Lucky seven. Silver hollow points.
没问题
Done.
你找我?
You wanted to see me?
有麻烦
We've got trouble.
晚上兼差打工吗 老大?
Doing a little moonlighting, chief?
该死
Shit!
你们在这里干什么?
What are you doing here?
说
Talk.
说出来
Spill it!
你心里明白
You know what we're doing.
里面是什么?
What's inside?
1号门里面是什么?
Now, what's behind door number one?
不能说 他们会杀了我
I can't tell you. They... They'll kill me.
杀你? 王八蛋 我更想杀你
Kill you? Motherfucker, I'll kill you.
我更喜欢
I'll just enjoy it better.
你知道该怎么做
You know the routine.
开灯
Lights.
我的天啊
God in heaven.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
鲜血畜牧场
It's a blood-farming facility.
我们觉得一个个猎杀效率...
Vampires decided that hunting humans on a piecemeal basis was...
...太低
...too inefficient.
猎物能养活不一定要杀掉?
Why kill your prey when you can keep them alive?
在最佳状况下...
Under optimal conditions, a donor can generate...
...一个可以生产50到100品脱的血
...anywhere from 50 to 100 pints of blood.
生产力很好
Productive.
这些人哪来的?
Where do you get all these people?
每个大城市都有物流中心
They got processing centers in every major city.
美国随时都有两三百万...
At any given time, there's what...
...无家可归的游民?
...2, 3 million homeless wandering around America?
他们直接在街上抓人
They just pull them in off the streets.
有谁在乎他们
Nobody cares about them.
这也算是解决社会问题
We're doing this country a service, really.
吸血鬼的终极方案
Vampire final solution.
他们有意识吗?
Are they aware?
有感觉吗?
Do they feel anything?
由药物引入深度昏迷
They're in a chemical-induced coma.
他们都已脑死
They're brain-dead.
给我看清楚
Look at this.
你也想要这种未来吗?
This the future you want?
他们以后也会给你一个位置?
Do you think that they have a place for you in their future?
我们没有选择余地
We don't have a choice.
他们赢定了 你看不出来吗?
They're going to win. Can't you see that?
他回来了
He's come back!
谁也挡不住他
There's nothing stopping them now.
有我在
There's me.
走
Go.
我给你20秒
You got 20 seconds.
二十秒
Twenty.
停止运作密码是什么?
Shutdown password, what is it?
"收获"
Harvest.
输进去
Put it in.
我们走
Let's go.
你去那里了? 我在你背后
Where'd you go? See? I turned my back on you.
- 你赢了  - 再一次 再一次
- You win.  - One more, one more.
"现在 诺姆国王坏事做尽...
"Now, Nome King, having never tried to be good...
...是个很坏的国王
...was very bad indeed.
他决定要征服欧兹仙境...
Having decided to conquer the land of Oz...
...并完全摧毁翡翠城..."
...and to destroy Emerald City..."
根据那篇文章
I get that paper and I'm chillln'on the low
我需要很多钱
All I need is more money, more
- 这不是打电玩  - 这不是打电玩
- This ain't no video game.  - This ain't no video game.
哦
Oh!
现在 来吧
Come on, now.
老兄 你不是死了吗
Dude, you're dead.
妈妈 灯光好奇怪
Mom, the lights are weird.
怎么了?
What do you mean?
一闪一闪的
They're going on and off.
你们两个?
Guys?
柔伊 你快走 快躲起来 好吗?
Zoe, I want you to go, and I want you to hide, okay?
照我以前说的去躲起来 快
Like we talked about. Go on.
柔伊？
Zoe?
快出去 柔伊
Get out of here, Zoe!
藏起来 该死
Hide! God dammit, Zoe!
不太对劲
Something's not right.
金恩
King!
柔伊
Zoe?
Zoe.
柔伊
Zoe?
惠斯勒
Whistler.
(不朽终归应得之人)
替她报仇
Use it.
走开 狗狗
Back off, pooch.
上帝啊
Jesus Christ!
出了什么事?
What the fuck?
- 乖狗狗  - 怎么回事?
- Good dog.  - What the fuck?
它叫小精灵
His name's Pac-Man.
它身上有吸血鬼基因 实验性的
We've been porting the vampire gene into other species. Experimenting.
你制造了一只吸血狗?
You made a goddamn vampire Pomeranian?
是啊
Yeah.
很可爱吧?
Precious, isn't he?
这要看你问谁...
Well, that depends who you ask, because clearly...
...因为它的老二比你大
...this dog has a bigger dick than you.
你什么时候看过我的老二?
And when the fuck did you see my dick, fuck-face?
喔
Ow!
我在跟她讲话
I was talking to her!
可怜的金恩
Poor King.
你快完蛋了
You look so distraught.
- 嗯  - 那把椅子给我
- Unh!  - Give me that chair.
你尝起来没味道 亲爱的
You're tasting a little bland, lover.
你都没吃脂肪酸吗?
Are you getting enough fatty acids in your diet?
淡水鱼海鱼你都不吃吗?
Have you tried lake trout?
鲭鱼?
Mackerel?
要不要尝尝...
How about you take a sugar-frosted fuck...
...我老二的味道?
...off the end of my dick?
大家不要再提老二了好不好?
And how about everyone here not saying the word "dick" anymore?
我的阳具崇拜症快发作了
It provokes my envy.
告诉我们关于刀锋 金恩
Tell us about Blade, King.
刀锋用这种武器想干什么?
What's this weapon he's been planning?
我可以跟你说两件事
I can tell you two things.
一...
One...
...你的发型很好笑
...your hairdo is ridiculous.
二 我吃了很多大蒜 我刚放了一个屁
Two, I ate a lot of garlic, and I just farted.
不响但很臭
Silent but deadly.
快说 该死的小白脸
Spit it out, you fucking fruitcake.
好了 我跟你们说武器
All right! Fuck! I'll tell you about the weapon.
那是新口味的结晶配方
It's a new flavor-crystal formula.
巧克力风味加倍 一半热量
Twice the chocolatey goodness, half the calories.
还可以防止蛀牙
Plus, it helps prevent tooth decay. There.
算你有种 金恩
You're brave, King.
你等着瞧
I'll give you that.
尽管你满口屁话...
But underneath all that swagger...
...我知道你真的怕什么
...l know what you really fear.
我知道你的致命伤
What would hurt you more than anything else.
你不想再当吸血鬼 对吧?
You don't wanna go back to being one of us, do you?
我要再咬你一口 金恩
I'm gonna bite you again, King.
留你一个人在这里变身
And I'm gonna leave you here while you turn.
我每天都会来看你...
I'm going to watch you day after day...
...看你的嗜血欲望一天天变强
...as the thirst keeps building and building.
然后...
And then...
...当你再也受不了时...
...when you can't stand it anymore...
...我会把那个小女孩带来...
...l'm gonna bring the little girl in here...
...让你饱餐一顿
...for you to feed on.
你喜欢吗 金恩?
Would you like that, King?
享受杀她的滋味吗?
Would you enjoy taking her life?
我在等你回答呢 宝贝
Now we're getting somewhere, my pet.
你还好吧?
Are you all right?
很好 我没事
Yeah. I'll be fine.
不要被愤怒控制
Don't let it turn inward.
我已经被控制了 从我拥有这样东西的记忆以来
Ever since I can remember, I've had this....
就只有这把刀...
I've had this knife...
...我只要有一口气
...of sadness in my heart.
我就是那么地坚强不会被打倒
And as long as it's there, I'm strong and I'm untouchable.
但是当我抛下...
But the moment that I take it out...
...我会死
...I'll just die.
- 他是自己人  - 我叫寇德
- He's one of ours.  - My name is Caulder.
今晚当你的司机
I'll be your driver this evening.
桑莫菲有留话给你们
Sommerfield left you a video message.
看到这录影时我已经死了
If you're watching this, I'm already dead.
答应我 帮我好好照顾柔伊?
If Zoe's alive, I want you to promise me that you'll take care of her, okay?
我正在帮她念欧兹的故事
I've been reading her the Oz books every night.
刚开始念欧兹的翡翠城
We just started reading The Emerald City of Oz.
就是诺姆国王那一段
You know, the one with the Nome King.
我相信有一支"晨星"病毒有效
I think I've managed to cultivate a workable strain of the DayStar virus.
我将它植在寇德身上...
As a precaution, I transmitted the genetic sequence to Caulder...
...预防库存被摧毁
...in case our main stock was destroyed.
为了达到最高致命率...
In order for it to achieve maximum lethality...
...必须混入德瑞克的鲜血
...you're gonna need to interfuse it with Drake's blood.
如果发挥作用 邻近的吸血鬼...
Now, if it works, every vampire in the immediate vicinity...
...将立即死亡
...should die almost instantly.
另外有件事
There's one other thing.
刀锋 你需要了解
Blade, you need to know...
...病毒可能也会杀死你
...there's a chance the virus could destroy you too.
因为你是混种人...
Because you're a hybrid...
...不知道你的免疫系统受得了吗
...I'm not sure if your immune system will be able to tolerate it.
抱歉 没有时间充分做试验
I'm sorry. We just didn't have enough time to properly test it.
要检查病毒发射器吗?
So shall we take a look at the plague arrow?
时间只够生产少数"晨星"
I only had time to fabricate a small amount of DayStar.
可是 我把它装在...
However, I was able to outfit it...
...高压气体发射器里...
...in a compressed-gas projectile...
...用四管来福枪就可以发射 弓也可以
...that can be shot from one of the four-barrel rifles or a bow.
总之 必须一发命中
Either way, you must be sure that the shot counts.
没有第二次机会
You will simply not have enough for a sencond shot.
你知道我是谁吗?
Do you know who I am?
你是诺姆国王
You're the Nome King.
恩
Huh.
诺姆国王
The Nome King.
你嘴真甜
How sweet.
告诉我 孩子 你想死吗
Tell me, child, do you want to die?
我不怕
I'm not afraid.
我会上天堂
I'll go to heaven.
没有天堂
There is no heaven.
也没有上帝或天使
No God, no angels.
你的未来什么都没有
The only thing in your future is nothingness.
但如果你能改变它呢?
But what if you could change that?
但如果你能永远当个小孩呢?
What if you could remain a child forever?
你不喜欢吗?
Wouldn't you like that?
想不想接受这个礼物?
Wouldn't you accept that gift?
我朋友会来杀你
My friends are coming to kill you.
(更新爱碧IPod里的歌曲)
你会后悔的
Gonna be sorry you did that.
怎么说?
Why?
没人会来救你的 废人
Nobody's coming for you, King Shit.
他们会来
Sure they are.
天哪
God.
有件事你需要知道 关于我们夜行者...
See, one of the things you fuckheads need to know about us Nightstalkers...
...如果加入夜行者俱乐部 我们有送精美的来店礼
...is that when you join our club, you get all sorts of groovy little door prizes.
其中之一就是植入式追踪晶片
And one of them is this nifty little tracking node surgically implanted is your body.
- 胡说八道  - 好
- Bulishit.  - Yeah.
如果有人失踪...
See, when one of us goes missing...
...其他人透过卫星...
...the others, they just dial up the satellite...
...取得定位
...which is in space.
马上就...
And then, presto...
...前来救援
...instant cavalry.
你以为我在说笑话吗?
You like that, huh?
回去说给你妹妹听
Go fuck your sister.
好吧 金恩
Okay, King.
你的追踪晶片在哪里?
Where is this tracking node of yours?
在我性感的左臀
It's in my left ass cheek.
好极了
Fine.
在我性感的右臀
It's in my right ass cheek.
好的 这次说真的
Okay, I'm... Okay, seriously, now.
我说在右臀 在屁屁Hello Kitty刺青里面
It's in the meat of my butt, just below the Hello Kitty tattoo.
脱下我的小裤裤你就知道了
Seriously, just pull down my tighty-whities and see for yourself.
够了 不好笑
Enough! It's not funny anymore!
确实不好笑 妹子
No, it's not, you horse-humping bitch!
但几秒钟之后就好笑了
But it will be a few seconds from now.
因为你的喉咙已经发痒了...
That tickle that you're feeling in the back of your throat right now...
- 嗯  - ...胶状银微粒
- Unh.  - ...that's atomized colloidal silver.
已经侵入空调系统...
It's being pumped through the air-conditioning system...
...你这该死的淫魔
...you cock-juggling thundercunt!
这表示我的救兵...
Which means the fat lady should be singing...
...快到了
...right about now.
嘿 可恶
Heh. This is awkward.
你有手机吗?
Do you have a cell phone?
嗯...
Um...
可以帮个忙吗
Little help here.
- 你没事吧?  - 是的
- Are you all right?  - Yeah.
- 柔伊在哪里?  - 被德瑞克抓走了
- Where's Zoe?  - Drake's got her.
了解
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
你的玩具带来了
Brought your toys.
想办法跟上
Try to keep up.
- 爱碧  - 嘿
- Abby!  - Hey.
你没事吧?
You okay?
我们马上来救你
Okay. Let's get you out of here.
小心
Watch out!
见鬼
Fuck me.
该死 该死
Fuck me sideways.
哦 天
Oh, yeah.
你是很可爱的狗?
He's a cute little guy, aren't you?
狗狗乖
Good little puppies.
待在这里
Yeah, you're gonna stay.
不要动
You stay.
笑得很可爱 很好
Oh. There's a pretty smile. Yeah.
我要去...
I'm going to, uh....
嘿 臭小子 有看到我的狗吗?
Hey, dickface, you seen my dog?
去大厅找找看?
Have you tried the lobby?
谢谢
Thank you.
见鬼...
Fuck...
- 来吧 金恩  - ...这里
- Come on, King.  - ...this.
刀锋
Blade.
准备受死了吗?
Ready to die?
一出生就准备好了 混蛋
I was born ready, motherfucker.
"混蛋"
"Motherfucker."
这名字不错
I like that.
我的手臂断了
Broke my arm.
想死了吗 混蛋?
Are you ready to die, motherfucker?
别管它
Give it up.
起来 快起来啊 金恩
Come on. Give it up, King.
起来吧 起来
Give it up. Give it up.
起来
Give it up.
挺住 亲爱的
Hang in there, kitten.
我找人救你
I'll get help.
很好笑 不是吗?
Funny, isn't it?
我族人一直想创造新吸血鬼...
All this time, my people were trying to create a new kind of vampire...
...你不正是最好的品种吗
...when one already existed.
我不需要活下去
I don't need to survive.
你就是我们族人的未来
The future of our race rests with you.
你跟恐惧对抗
You fought with honor.
我尊敬你这点
I respect that.
我送你一个临别礼物
Allow me a parting gift.
作为纪念
But remember this:
迟早有一天...
Sooner or later...
...嗜血欲望会战胜一切
...the thirst always wins.
刀锋呢?
And Blade?
病毒并没有杀死他
The virus didn't kill him.
因为他是一个混血儿 他的心从来不会停止跳动
Because he was a hybrid, his heart never stopped beating.
只可能减慢
It simply slowed down.
所以他沉睡了 为了重生的一刻
And so he slept, waiting for the moment he could walk the earth again.